Register of the Kenneth Gibson Fuller collection
Hoover Institution Archives
- Serial Issues, 1964-1991 (Boxes 22-57)
  - Lado, 1971 (Box-folder 38: 4)
  - Lavender U., 1974-1975 (Box-folder 38: 5)
  - Lesbian Tide, 1975 (Box-folder 38: 6)
  - Leviathan, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 38: 7)
  - Liberation, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 38: 8)
  - Liberator, 1968 (Box-folder 38: 9)
  - Like It Is, 1971 (Box-folder 38: 10)
  - Los Angeles News Advocate, 1971 (Box-folder 38: 11)
  - Love Newspaper, 1969 (Box-folder 38: 12)
  - LSM News, 1974 (Box-folder 38: 13)
  - Madison Kaleidoscope, 1970 (Box-folder 38: 14)
  - Majority Report, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 38: 15)
  - Man and State, 1964 (Box-folder 38: 16)
  - Many Smokes, 1967 (Box-folder 38: 17)
  - Marin Women's News Journal, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 38: 18)
  - Marxist-Leninists Unite!, 1973 (Box-folder 38: 19)
  - The Match!, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 39: 1)
  - Matchbox, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 39: 2)
  - MDS Newsletter, 1968 (Box-folder 39: 3)
  - Mexican American News, 1969 (Box-folder 39: 4)
  - Michigan Free Press, 1975 (Box-folder 39: 5-8)
  - Midnight Special, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 39: 9)
  - Militant, 1970 (Box-folder 39: 10)
  - Mobarezé, 1970 (Box-folder 39: 11)
  - Mobilizer, 1967 (Box-folder 39: 12)
  - Momma, 1973 (Box-folder 40: 1)
  - Monroe Prison Sunfighter, 1974 (Box-folder 40: 2)
  - Montclair Press, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 40: 3)
  - Montclarion, 1966 (Box-folder 40: 4)
  - [More], 1974-1975 (Box-folder 40: 5)
  - NACLA's Latin America & Empire Report, 1973 (Box-folder 40: 6)
  - New America, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 40: 7)
  - New Left Notes, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 40: 8)
  - New Morning, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 40: 9-10)
  - New/Nueva Mission, 1968 (Box-folder 40: 11)
  - New Politics News, 1968 (Box-folder 40: 12)
  - New Solidarity, 1972-1980
    - 1972-1975 (Box-folder 40: 13)
    - 1980 (Box-folder 41: 1)
  - New Times, 1970 (Box-folder 41: 2)
  - New York City Star, 1974 (Box-folder 41: 3)
  - New York Free Press, 1968 (Box-folder 41: 4-5)
  - New Voice, 1971-1977 (Box-folder 41: 6)
  - News & Letters, 1969 (Box-folder 41: 7)
  - Newsletter, 1966 (Box-folder 41: 8)
  - Newsweek, 1970 (Box-folder 41: 9)
  - Newswest, 1976 (Box-folder 41: 10)
  - Night Times, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 41: 11)
  - NOLA Express, 1968 (Box-folder 41: 12)
  - North Beach Gull, 1971 (Box-folder 41: 13)
  - Northwest Passage, 1970 (Box-folder 41: 14)
  - Now Hear This!, 1970 (Box-folder 41: 15)
  - Oakland Times, 1970-1973
    - 1970-1971 (Box-folder 41: 16)
    - 1972-1973 (Box-folder 42: 1)
  - Obreros en marcha, 1975 (Box-folder 42: 2)
  - Off Our Backs, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 42: 3)
  - Open Cell, 1969 (Box-folder 42: 4)
  - Open City, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 42: 5-6)
  - Open Process, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 42: 7)
  - Openings, 1969 (Box-folder 42: 8)
  - Opposition West, 1966 (Box-folder 42: 9)
  - Organ, 1970 (Box-folder 42: 10)
  - Other Scenes, 1969 (Box-folder 42: 11)
  - Outcry!, 1969 (Box-folder 42: 12)
  - Outlaw, 1972-1976
    - 1972-1973 (Box-folder 43: 1)
    - 1974 (Box-folder 43: 2)
    - 1975-1976 (Box-folder 43: 3)
  - Pacific Sun, 1973-1975
    - 1973 (Box-folder 43: 4)
    - 1974 (Box-folder 43: 5-6)
    - 1974-1975 (Box-folder 43: 7)
  - Pack Rat, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 43: 8)
  - Palestine Resistance Bulletin, 1971 (Box-folder 43: 9)
  - Pamoja Venceremos, 1972 (Box-folder 44: 1)
  - Paper (East Lansing), 1966-1969 (Box-folder 44: 2)
  - Paper (Oakland), 1972 (Box-folder 44: 3)
  - Paper (Santa Monica), 1970 (Box-folder 44: 4)
  - Partisan (New York), 1968 (Box-folder 44: 5)
  - Partisan (San Francisco), 1969 (Box-folder 44: 6)
  - Patriot, 1970 (Box-folder 44: 7)
  - Peace and Freedom News (Berkeley, California), 1968 (Box-folder 44: 8)
  - Peace and Freedom News (Contra Costa, California), 1968 (Box-folder 44: 9)
  - Peace and Freedom News (Madison, Wisconsin), 1966 (Box-folder 44: 10)
  - Peace and Freedom Organizer, 1967 (Box-folder 44: 11)
  - Peace Mobilization Bulletin, 1970 (Box-folder 44: 12)
  - Peacemaker, 1969 (Box-folder 44: 13)
  - Peking Review, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 44: 14)
  - People Get Ready, 1970-1972
    - 1970-1971 (Box-folder 44: 15)
    - 1971 (Box-folder 45: 1)
    - 1971-1972 (Box-folder 45: 2)
  - People's America Daily News, 1970 (Box-folder 45: 3)
  - People's Crim, 1974 (Box-folder 45: 4)
  - People's Gay Sunshine, 1970 (Box-folder 45: 5)
  - People's Korea, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 45: 6)
  - People's News Service, 1971 (Box-folder 45: 7)
  - People's Vanguard, 1974 (Box-folder 45: 8)
  - People's Voice, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 45: 9)
  - Perspectiva mundial, 1978 (Box-folder 45: 10)
  - Petal Paper, 1967 (Box-folder 45: 11)
  - P.F.L.P. Bulletin (Popular Front for the Liberation of Palestine), 1974-1976 (Box-folder 45: 12)
  - Philippine Liberation Courier, 1977 (Box-folder 45: 13)
  - Picket Line, 1970 (Box-folder 45: 14)
  - Piedmont-Montclair Times, 1984 (Box-folder 45: 15)
  - Pioneer, 1969 (Box-folder 45: 16)
  - Plain Rapper, 1969 (Box-folder 45: 17)
  - Plain Speaking, 1982 (Box-folder 45: 18)
  - Planet, 1969 (Box-folder 45: 19)
  - Plexus, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 46: 1-2)
  - Point of Production, 1972 (Box-folder 46: 3)
  - Posición centroamericana, 1977 (Box-folder 46: 4)
  - P.O.W., 1971 (Box-folder 46: 5)
  - Prensa popular, 1971 (Box-folder 46: 6)
  - Prisma, 1974 (Box-folder 46: 7)
  - Probe, 1970 (Box-folder 46: 8)
  - Progressive Worker, 1967 (Box-folder 46: 9)
  - Punji Stick, 1972 (Box-folder 46: 10)
  - Radical America, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 46: 11)
  - Radical Rag, 1970 (Box-folder 46: 12)
  - RAM-PAGES, 1970 (Box-folder 46: 13)
  - Realist, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 46: 14)
  - Rebel Worker, 1978 (Box-folder 46: 15)
  - Recorder 70, 1970 (Box-folder 46: 16)
  - Red Balloon, 1972 (Box-folder 46: 17)
  - Red Guard, 1969 (Box-folder 46: 18)
  - Red Line Newsletter, 1969 (Box-folder 46: 19)
  - Red Papers, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 47: 1)
  - Red Sky Blue Sky, 1970 (Box-folder 47: 2)
  - Red Tide, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 47: 3)
  - Renaissance, 1970 (Box-folder 47: 4)
  - Report on Greece, 1967 (Box-folder 47: 5)
  - Resist, 1967 (Box-folder 47: 6)
  - Resistance (anti-draft), 1968 (Box-folder 47: 7)
  - Resistance (Iranian students), 1972-1977 (Box-folder 47: 8)
  - Resistance/Resistencia (New York City), 1977 (Box-folder 47: 9)
  - Resistance (Santa Cruz, CA), 1974 (Box-folder 47: 10)
  - Resistance Newsletter (Box-folder 47: 11)
  - Resurrection, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 47: 12)
  - Resuscitator, 1976 (Box-folder 47: 13)
  - Revolutionary Communist Youth Newsletter, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 47: 14)
  - Revolutionary Youth, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 47: 15)
  - Revolutionary Youth Movement, 1970 (Box-folder 47: 16)
  - Richmond Black Belt, 1968 (Box-folder 48: 1)
  - Right On! (Christian), 1969-1974 (Box-folder 48: 2)
  - Right On! (Revolutionary Peoples Communications Network), 1971 (Box-folder 48: 3)
  - Right-On Post, 1970 (Box-folder 48: 4)
  - Rip Off, 1969 (Box-folder 48: 5)
  - RT: A Journal of Radical Therapy, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 48: 6)
  - Sadvipra, 1975 (Box-folder 48: 7)
  - San Diego Free Press, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 48: 8)
  - San Francisco Bay Area Journalism Review, 1972 (Box-folder 48: 9)
  - San Francisco Express Times--Telegraph Avenue Edition, 1969 (Box-folder 48: 10)
  - San Francisco Fault, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 48: 11)
  - San Francisco Free Press, 1970 (Box-folder 48: 12)
  - San Francisco Good Times (Box-folder 48: 13)
  - San Francisco Journal, 1976-1977
    - 1976 (Box-folder 48: 14)
    - 1977 (Box-folder 49: 1-2)
  - San Francisco Phoenix, 1972-1974
    - 1972-1973 (Box-folder 49: 3)
    - 1973 (Box-folder 49: 4)
    - 1974 (Box-folder 49: 5-6)
    - 1974 (Box-folder 50: 1)
  - San Francisco's Openings, 1970 (Box-folder 50: 2)
  - San Jose Maverick, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 50: 3-4)
  - Saut Al-Thawra, 1975 (Box-folder 50: 5)
  - Science for the People, 1972 (Box-folder 50: 6)
  - Scientist and Citizen, 1967 (Box-folder 50: 7)
  - Scientists for Social and Political Action Newsletter, 1969 (Box-folder 50: 8)
  - Sechaba, 1971 (Box-folder 50: 9)
  - Second Page, 1971 (Box-folder 50: 10)
  - Sedition, 1974 (Box-folder 50: 11)
  - Seize the Time, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 50: 12)
  - Serve the People, 1969 (Box-folder 50: 13)
  - S.F. Oracle, 1966 (Box-folder 50: 14)
  - Simple Living, 1974 (Box-folder 51: 1)
  - Sin Fronteras, 1974 (Box-folder 51: 2)
  - Sister, 1975 (Box-folder 51: 3)
  - SLATE, 1964-1974 (Box-folder 51: 4-5)
  - Socialist Action (Berkeley), 1968 (Box-folder 51: 6)
  - Socialist Action (San Francisco), 1984 (Box-folder 51: 7)
  - Socialist Appeal, 1976 (Box-folder 51: 8)
  - Socialist Leader, 1968 (Box-folder 51: 9)
  - Socialist Voice, 1968 (Box-folder 51: 10)
  - Soledad Brothers Newsletter, 1971 (Box-folder 51: 11)
  - Solidarity (Eugene, Oregon), 1971 (Box-folder 51: 12)
  - Solidarity (Montreal), 1971 (Box-folder 51: 13)
  - Solidarity (San Francisco), 1970 (Box-folder 51: 14)
  - South Viet Nam in Struggle, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 51: 15)
  - Southern Africa News (Box-folder 51: 16)
  - Southern Patriot, 1969 (Box-folder 51: 17)
  - Spare Change, 1970 (Box-folder 51: 18)
  - Spark (Detroit), 1977 (Box-folder 51: 19)
  - Spark (Southeast Asian students), 1970-1972 (Box-folder 51: 20)
  - Spartan Daily, 1972 (Box-folder 51: 21)
  - Sparticist, 1965-1981 (Box-folder 51: 22)
  - Spectrum, 1974 (Box-folder 51: 23)
  - Spider, 1965 (Box-folder 52: 1)
  - Spur, 1965 (Box-folder 52: 2)
  - Staff, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 52: 3-4)
  - Stars and Strikes, 1976 (Box-folder 52: 5)
  - State of the Union, 1977 (Box-folder 52: 6)
  - Steps, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 52: 7)
  - Straightqueer, 1972 (Box-folder 52: 8)
  - Street Art News, 1975 (Box-folder 52: 9)
  - Street Journal, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 52: 10)
  - Strike Bulletin, 1969 (Box-folder 52: 11)
  - Struggle!, 1975 (Box-folder 52: 12)
  - Student Action, 1968 (Box-folder 52: 13)
  - Student Mobilizer Wall Poster, 1969 (Box-folder 52: 14)
  - Student Voice, 1965 (Box-folder 52: 15)
  - Sun-Reporter, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 52: 16)
  - Susan Saxe Defense Committee Newsletter, 1976 (Box-folder 52: 17)
  - Taishū, 1973 (Box-folder 53: 1)
  - Task Force, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 53: 2)
  - Telegraph Avenue Liberation Front Manual, 1969 (Box-folder 53: 3)
  - Telegraph Monthly, 1971 (Box-folder 53: 4)
  - Tenants Rising, 1969 (Box-folder 53: 5)
  - Thang, 1971 (Box-folder 53: 6)
  - Third World News, 1971 (Box-folder 53: 7)
  - Through to Victory, 1971 (Box-folder 53: 8)
  - Tie Line, 1976 (Box-folder 53: 9)
  - Tiger Paper, 1975 (Box-folder 53: 10)
  - Tin Tan, 1975 (Box-folder 53: 11)
  - To Free Mankind, 1970 (Box-folder 53: 12)
  - Together, 1969 (Box-folder 53: 13)
  - Tooth and Nail, 1970 (Box-folder 53: 14)
  - Touch, 1971 (Box-folder 53: 15)
  - Trade Union Action & Democracy, 1970 (Box-folder 53: 16)
  - Transport Worker, 1970 (Box-folder 53: 17)
  - Travisty, 1973 (Box-folder 53: 18)
  - Tricontinental, 1971 (Box-folder 53: 19)
  - Triple Jeopardy, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 53: 20-21)
  - UCLA Daily Bruin, 1969 (Box-folder 54: 1)
  - UConn Free Press, 1970 (Box-folder 54: 2)
  - Uhuru, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 54: 3)
  - ¡Unidad!, 1968 (Box-folder 54: 4)
  - Union W.A.G.E., 1972-1977 (Box-folder 54: 5-6)
  - United Irishman, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 54: 7)
  - University Guardian, 1972 (Box-folder 54: 8)
  - University Unionist, 1971 (Box-folder 54: 9)
  - Up against the Bulkhead, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 54: 10)
  - Up from the Bottom, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 54: 11)
  - U.S. China Friendship Newsletter, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 54: 12)
  - U.S. Farm News, 1965 (Box-folder 54: 13)
  - USLA Reporter, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 54: 14)
  - U.W.O.C. National News, 1975 (Box-folder 54: 15)
  - Venceremos, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 54: 16)
  - Veteran, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 54: 17)
  - Veterans Stars & Stripes for Peace, 1967 (Box-folder 54: 18)
  - Viet Report, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 55: 1)
  - Viet/Nam Bulletin, 1966 (Box-folder 55: 2)
  - Viet-Nam Bulletin, 1965 (Box-folder 55: 3)
  - Vietnam Courier (Box-folder 55: 4)
  - Vietnam Day Committee News, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 55: 5)
  - Vietnam GI, 1968 (Box-folder 55: 6)
  - Vietnam Newsletter, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 55: 7)
  - Vietnam Observer, 1967 (Box-folder 55: 8)
  - Vietnam Summer News, 1967 (Box-folder 55: 9)
  - Vietnam Veterans against the War/Winter Soldier Organization, 1974 (Box-folder 55: 10)
  - Vocations for Social Change, 1969-1972
    - 1969-1970 (Box-folder 55: 11)
    - 1971 (Box-folder 55: 12)
    - 1971-1972 (Box-folder 55: 13)
  - Voice of the Congress, 1976 (Box-folder 55: 14)
  - War behind Walls, 1971 (Box-folder 55: 15)
  - Warpath, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 55: 16)
  - Washington Free Press, 1968 (Box-folder 55: 17)
  - Washoi, 1969 (Box-folder 56: 1)
  - Wassaja, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 56: 2)
  - Weapon, 1965 (Box-folder 56: 3)
  - Weekly Golden Bear, 1969 (Box-folder 56: 4)
  - Wei Min, 1971-1975
    - 1971 (Box-folder 56: 5)
    - 1972 (Box-folder 56: 6-7)
    - 1973-1975 (Box-folder 56: 8)
  - Wildcat, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 56: 9-10)
  - Wildcat Women, 1970 (Box-folder 56: 11)
  - Win, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 56: 12)
  - Western Socialist, 1974 (Box-folder 57: 1)
  - Whisper, 1972 (Box-folder 57: 2)
  - Women United, 1974 (Box-folder 57: 3)
  - Women's Page, 1971 (Box-folder 57: 4)
  - Women's Press, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 57: 5)
  - Workers' Action, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 57: 6)
  - Workers' Press, 1977 (Box-folder 57: 7)
  - Workers Vanguard, 1969 (Box-folder 57: 8)
  - WorkForce, 1972 (Box-folder 57: 9-10)
  - Writ, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 57: 11)
  - WRL News, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 57: 12)
  - Yipster Times, 1974 (Box-folder 57: 13)
  - Y.L.O., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 57: 14)
  - Yodeler, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 57: 15)
  - Young Bolshevik, 1977 (Box-folder 57: 16)
  - Young Communist, 1978 (Box-folder 57: 17)
  - Young Socialist, 1975 (Box-folder 57: 18)
  - Young Socialist Organizer, 1970 (Box-folder 57: 19)
  - Young Worker, 1977 (Box-folder 57: 20)
  - Youth in Struggle, 1970 (Box-folder 57: 21)